There's no humanitarian crisis right now in Gaza.
There's no humanitarian crisis right now in Gaza?
Correct.
Can you explain what you mean?
I'm saying there's no humanitarian crisis.
We've asked people to move, there's water, and there's electricity.
All the doctors that we've...
First of all, the fact that these people be claiming they're indigenous to this land
and everybody got a different accent.
I done heard South African accents right here.
We got like a Scottish flavor accent.
You're hearing British accents.
I have yet to hear an actual Hebrew accent from anyone in leadership.
Netanyahu's from freaking Boston.
So that's one.
Two, what in the Jedi mind trick?
These aren't the droids you're looking for.
Are we experiencing?
There is a humanitarian crisis in Gaza.
There's no food.
There's no water.
There ain't even any maxi pads.
Everything they do is an exercise in attempting to let genocide be okay.
It is maddening to watch and we can't stop it.